Irene Wu

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Phone: 778-859-9204

Email: irenewu222@gmail.com

Website: www.rostrae.ca

Skills

Front-end Coding Web Development UX/UI Design Responsive Design User Testing

HTML, CSS
Sass
Javascript, jQuery
Next.js, React.js
Expo
RESTful API
Github, Git
Figma
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Effects
Adobe Audition
Adobe InDesign

Communication
Collaboration
Organization
Time Management
Problem Solving

Languages

English Mandarin

Highlights

Front-end web developer with two years of experience in closely collaborating with teams in designing and developing interactive and responsive cross platform web applications. Competent in developing web applications incorporating a range of technologies as well as modern libraries and frameworks. Eager to learn new things and use my skills to create quality cross platform web applications.

Education

Digital Design & Development Diploma

BRITISH COLUMBIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY | SEPTEMBER 2020 - MAY 2022

- Designed and developed interactive, responsive websites.
- Collaborated closely with team members for 5+ projects.
- · Wrote clean and organized code while using the best practices.
- Developed strong time management through collaboration with multiple teams in a tight schedule.

Project Experience

Frontend Developer, UX/UI Designer

KALM | SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

- Designed and developed a user-friendly, responsive web app.
- Created reusable UI components using React and Styled-components.
- Worked closely with full-stack developers about the design and front-end.

Lead Frontend Developer, UX/UI Designer

REVAMP | JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

- Conducted thorough user testing to create a user-friendly application.
- Polished the front-end to ensure all functionalities are working.
- Collaborated closely with team members remotely, ensuring everyone is on track.

Work Experience

Sales Associate

KINS FARM MARKET | SEPTEMBER 2017 - AUGUST 2020

- Built rapport and answering customers questions.
- · Maintained positive attitude and helped others when in need.
- Developed observant skills by completing tasks while under pressure with thoroughness and accuracy.